Guide to the Adler hip hop archive, circa 1970-2013.
Adler hip hop archive
- Series I. News Files
  - News Files 1980s
    - Performer Names I-P
      - LL Cool J
        - LL Cool J, "Nitro" tour '89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - LL Cool J '90, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - LL Cool J '91, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - LL Cool J '92, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - LL Cool J '93, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
        - LL Cool J business documents '93, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 5
        - LL Cool J FUBU ads, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - LL Cool J business documents '94, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 6
        - LL Cool J '95, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
        - LL Cool J business documents '95, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 7
        - LL Cool J '96, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
        - LL Cool J business documents '96, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 8
        - LL Cool J '97, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
        - LL Cool J business documents '97, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 9
        - LL Cool J '98, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
        - LL Cool J '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
        - LL Cool J '00, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
        - LL Cool J '01, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
        - LL Cool J '02, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
        - LL Cool J '03-'04, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 27)
        - LL Cool J '05, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 28)
        - LL Cool J '06-'12, 2006-2012 (Box 7, Folder 29)
        - LL Cool J's sidekick, E-Love (later known as D. Earl Matthias), 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 30)
        - LL Cool J '13, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Low Profile, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Lovebug Starski, 1984-1986, 1996-2012 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Hurby Luvbug, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Hurby Luvbug, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Monica Lynch, 1993-1999 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - MC Lyte, 1988-2012 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Disco King Mario, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Ralph McDaniels, 1992-1994, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Malcolm McLaren, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Malcolm X, "No Sell Out", 1983-1954 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - MCII, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Mr. Magic, 1981-1999, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Bonz Malone, 1990-2012 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Mantronix, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Marley Marl, 1989-2006 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Masters of the Beat, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Mean Machine, 1982, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Melanin, 1992, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Ms. Melodie, 1989-1990, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Ric Menello, 2010-2013 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - David Mills, 1986-1990, 2010-2013 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Mitch-Ski, No Date (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Monie Love, 1989-1993, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Patrick Moxey, 1988-1989, 2000-2007 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Music in Action, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - "Bring the Noise" (book), 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Newcleus, 1984-1985, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Peter Noel, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - NWA
        - NWA-bios and photos, No Date (Box 7, Folder 60)
        - NWA '89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 61)
        - NWA '90, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 62)
        - NWA '91, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 63)
        - NWA '91 (U.K.), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 64)
        - NWA '92-'94, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 65)
        - NWA '00-'12, 2000-2012 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Old School (general), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Original Concept, 1985-1989, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Bert Padell, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Paradise Garage (nightclub), 1992, 2000, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Paris (San Francisco rapper)
        - Paris working papers, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Paris, label press materials, correspondence, research '91-'92, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Paris press '90-'92, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Paris press '93, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Paris, press reports, etc '93, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Paris, press releases, speeches, etc '93, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
        - Paris '95-'08, 1995-2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
        - Paris lyrics, 1992, No Date (Box 8, Folder 8)
          Includes the transcript of an interview with Paris
        - Paris ad, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Paris Italian press, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Paris Omega Boys Club, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        - Paris '94, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - PM Dawn
        - PM Dawn interview, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
        - PM Dawn photos, 1993, No Date (Box 8, Folder 14)
        - PM Dawn attacked by KRS-One, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
        - PM Dawn press, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
        - PM Dawn label correspondence, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - "Poetic Justice" (movie), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Poor Righteous Teachers, 1990-2011 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Scott Poulson-Bryant article "Scott's Arc" in America magazine, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Prince Akeem, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Priority Records, 1989, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Profile Records, 1985-2012 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Prophets of the City, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Public Enemy
        - Public Enemy in Los Angeles, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
          Photos by Deacon Chapin
        - Public Enemy in Cleveland - photos, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
        - Public Enemy with Charles Yancey of the Boston City Council - photo, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 27)
        - Public Enemy photos, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
        - Public Enemy press photos (for Wax Poetics magazine), No Date; CD-2092-2093 (Box 8, Folder 28)
        - Transcript of Chuck D interview by John Leland for Spin magazine, No Date (Box 8, Folder 29)
        - Public Enemy '87, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 30)
        - PE U.K. press '87, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
        - Public Enemy newspaper coverage '88, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 32)
        - Public Enemy magazine coverage '88, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 33)
        - Public Enemy at Rikers Island, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 34)
        - Public Enemy bios, press releases, ads, correspondence, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
        - Public Enemy '88, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
        - Agreement with Experience Music Project for the display of handwritten lyrics to "Nation of Millions….", 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 37)
        - Handwritten lyrics to all songs on "Nation of Millions…", 1988 (Box 8, Folder 38)
        - Public Enemy '89, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
        - Public Enemy press releases '89, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
        - Public Enemy targeted by Mordechai Levy of the Jewish Defense League, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 41)
        - Public Enemy '89, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 42)
        - Public Enemy (U.K. press), 2005 (Box 8, Folder 43)
        - Public Enemy Washington Times, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
        - Public Enemy foreign press, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 45)
        - Harry Allen faxes '90-'91, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 46)
        - Public enemy magazine coverage '90, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 47)
        - Public Enemy newspaper coverage '90, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 48)
        - Public Enemy '91, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - Public Enemy '92, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        - Public Enemy '93, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        - Public Enemy '95, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - Public Enemy '95, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - Public Enemy '96, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Public Enemy '97, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
        - Public Enemy '98, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        - Public Enemy '99, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        - Public Enemy '00-'09, 2000-2009 (Box 9, Folder 10)
        - Public Enemy '10-'12, 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 11)
        - Public Enemy '13, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Pumpkin, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Performer Names Q-Z
      - Rakamoto, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Rap (miscellaneous), 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Rap tours and shows, 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - "Rappin'" (movie), 1985, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Rappin' Duke, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Reality Records, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Rebel MC, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Red Alert
        - Red Alert, 1985-2012 (Box 9, Folder 21)
        - Red Alert in Wax Poetics (Issue 19), No Date; CD-2104 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Redhead Kingpin, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Simone Reyes, 1988, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Sylvia Rhone, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Bobby Robinson/Enjoy Records, 1981, 2006-2011 (Box 9, Folder 25)
        Also includes a publicity photo of Bobby Robinson from c. 1940s or 1950s.
      - Roxanne Shante, 1985-2009 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - The Real Roxanne, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Rock Steady Crew, 1992-2010 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Rick Rubin
        - Rick Rubin '85-'89, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
        - Rick Rubin '90-'99, 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
        - Rick Rubin '00-'09, 2000-2009 (Box 9, Folder 31)
        - Rick Rubin '10-'13, 2010-2013 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Rush Productions/Rush Artist Management/Russell Simmons/Def Jam Recordings
        - Rush/Russ Slides, c. 1985 (Box 9, Folder 33)
        - Rush Biz Press Campaign, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
        - Rush Producers Management, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
        - Russ photos, c. 1983-2002 (Box 9, Folder 36)
        - Russell Simmons photos, c. 1985-2005 (Box 9, Folder 37)
        - Miscellaneous Rush and Russell Simmons-related materials, c. 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 38)
          I am Hip-Hop, Phat Farm, Bre magazine, Island Def Jam Music Group booklet, The Spirit of Music Honoring Russell Simmons and Lyor Cohen, invitation to Art for Life
        - 360 Hip-Hop (electronic press kit), No Date; CD-2108 (Box 9, Folder 38)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '83-'85, 1983-1985, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 39)
        - Rush Productions special section, Billboard Magazine, April '85, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 40)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '86, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 41)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '87, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 42)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '88, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 43)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '89, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 44)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '90, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        - Rap community's response to Newsweek's anti-rap cover story, March 1990, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
        - Rush UK business documents '90, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 10
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '91, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '92, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '93, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - Robert Ford's proposal for a book about Russell Simmons '93, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
        - Def Jam leaves Sony '93, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '94, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        - Def College Jam '95, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        - DJ music publishing '95, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 11
        - Russell Simmons/Rush/Def Jam '95, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        - Def Jam's 10th anniversary, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
        - Def Jam Phactory, 1995; SR-6219 (Box 10, Folder 13)
        - Def Jam 10th anniversary box set, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - DJ reissues, 1993, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
          Includes track list for CDs
        - "Def Jam from the Jump" - Never-issued CDs of Def Jam's first eight singles, No Date; CD-2095-2097 (Box 10, Folder 15)
          T Larock and Jazzy Jay, LL Cool J, Beastie Boys, Jazzy JayMCA and Burzootie, Jimmy Spice, Hollis Crew
        - Russ/Russell Simmons '96, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
        - Rush/Russell Simmons '97, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
        - Russell Simmons '98, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
        - Russell Simmons '99, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
        - Russell and Lyor honored by the United Jewish Appeal, December '99, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
        - Draft of Lyor's speech for UJA event, No Date; FD-20 (Box 10, Folder 20)
        - Def Jam liner notes '00, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
        - Russell Simmons bio, '00, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
        - Def Jam press '00, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 23)
        - Def Jam '00, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 24)
        - 360 hiphop.com (electronic press kit), 2000; CD-2098 (Box 10, Folder 24)
        - Russell Simmons '01, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
        - "Def Jam Uncensored" on MTV '01, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 26)
        - Hip Hop Summit, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
        - Russell Simmons '02, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
        - "Russell Simmons's Def Poetry Jam on Broadway," '02, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
        - Russell Simmons '03, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)
        - Art Start - Hip Hop Project, 2003; CD-2099 (Box 10, Folder 30)
        - Russell Simmons/Mos Def Anti War Spot 2/10/03, 2003; CD-2109 (Box 10, Folder 30)
          Photos by Ray Tamarra
        - Russell Simmons Interview '03, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 31)
        - Def Jam 20th anniversary book, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 32)
        - Russell Simmons '04, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 33)
        - Russell Simmons '05, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 34)
        - Russell Simmons '06, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 35)
        - Simmons/Fenton, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 36)
        - Russell Simmons '07, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Russell Simmons '08, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - Def Jam '09, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - Russell Simmons '10-'11, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - "Running Russell Simmons" - Episodes 101 and 102, 2010; DVD-1170-1171 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - Russell Simmons '12, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Russell Simmons '13, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Simmons Jewelry Company, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Run-DMC
        - Run-DMC photos, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - Run-DMC photos, 1985 (2012) (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Run-DMC photos, July 23, 2012; CD-2100 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Run-DMC scans, No Date; CD-2101 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Jam Master Jay scans, No Date; CD-2102 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Run-DMC scans, photos flyers, magazine covers, No Date; DVD-1073 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Run-DMC press release photos, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
        - Fresno, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 12
        - National Alliance Business, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Run-DMC photos, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
          Includes news clippings. Information about an appearance on the Cosby Show in 1986
        - Run-DMC '83-'84, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - Fresh Fest 1 (1984), 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - Fresh Fest 2 (1985), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - Run-DMC on the cover of Newsday, '85, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
        - Live Aid '85, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 18)
        - Run-DMC '85, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
        - "Krush Groove Xmas Party" '85, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 20)
        - Benefit in Kansas City '86, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 21)
        - Run-DMC photo shoot, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
        - Rush/Def Jam at the Apollo Theater, '86, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
        - Run-DMC in England, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
        - Run-DMC at Long Beach August 1986, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
        - Run-DMC News clippings, No Date; CD-2103 (Box 11, Folder 25)
          Long Beach riot, Septemner 1986 / Run rape accusation, 1991
        - Run-DMC in Japan '86, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
        - Run-DMC - foreign language press, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
        - Run-DMC magazine coverage '86, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 28)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" disks, No Date; 4" floppy FD-12-19 (Box 11)
          Box of floppy disks - original and back-up
        - "Raising Hell Tour" '86, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Run-DMC newspaper coverage '86, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Run-DMC and Beastie Boys World Tour booklet, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Run-DMC magazine coverage '87, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Run-DMC and Beastie Boys "Together Forever" tour, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Run-DMC and Beastie Boys "Together Forever" tour promo, May '87 (60 seconds), No Date; DVD-1074 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Run-DMC press releases from the Howard Bloom Agency, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
          Includes slides of Run-DMC on Reading Rainbow
        - KDAY, L.A. Day of Peace '86, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - L.A. Street Scene Fest '86, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
          Grammy Award Nomination certificates for "Raising Hell"
        - Run-DMC/Adidas, 1987-2008 (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - Run-DMC newspaper coverage '87, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - "Together Forever" imitators '12, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 12)
        - MTV - Fourth Annual Video Music Award, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
          Agreement covering Run-DMC's appearance
        - Run-DMC "Christmas in Hollis", 1987-1988, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        - Run-DMC '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
        - Run-DMC newspaper coverage '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        - Run-DMC magazine coverage '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
        - "Run's House Tour" '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
        - Run-DMC Europe Tour '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
        - Contact sheets from the shooting of "Tougher Than Leather" (movie), No Date (Box 12, Folder 20)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" film script by Bill Adler and Lyor Cohen, No Date (Box 12, Folder 21)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" movie, 1986-1989, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 22)
        - Run-DMC with stars of "Ghostbusters II" photos by Juanita Cole, 1989, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
        - Run-DMC '89, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
        - Run-DMC '90, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
        - Run-DMC '91, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 26)
          Includes Run-DMC "Faces" masks
        - "Tougher Than Leather" film script by Rick Rubin and Ric Menello), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 27)
        - Black Beat Superstar Special #3, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
          Featuring Run-DMC
        - Treatment: Def Jam Summer '88 Tour Program, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 29)
          A 60-minute television show featuring Run-DMC, Public Enemy, DJ Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, and Stetsasonic
        - Run-DMC liner notes '91, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 30)
        - Run-DMC - Run accused of rape and acquitted, 199-1992 (Box 45, Folder 17)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45
        - Run-DMC '92, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 31)
        - Run-DMC newspaper coverage '93, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 32)
        - Run-DMC magazine coverage '93, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 33)
        - Run-DMC - Sony Lyrics "Down w/the King and Run's House (Box 13, Folder 1)
          Removed
        - Run-DMC - Once Again It's On, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Run-DMC, business correspondence/publicity materials '87, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - Run-DMC w/Michael Moore, 3/3/93, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Run-DMC in LA "Rap Pages" party c. 3/11/93, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - Run-DMC '94, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - Run-DMC '95, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
        - Run-DMC/Profile '94-'95, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - Run-DMC '96, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        - JMJ Records, legal documents '96, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 13
        - Run-DMC '97, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - Rev Run Xmas Record '97, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - DMC script pages, No Date (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" press materials on the movie, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Photo Releases, No Date (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - Run Lyrics Permissions, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
        - Run-DMC '98/'99, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
        - Run-DMC '00, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 18)
        - Run-DMC '01, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
        - Run-DMC '02, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
        - Jam Master Jay killed, 10/30/02, newspapers/magazines, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
        - Jam Master Jay, killed 10/30/02 (print-outs), 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
        - Jan Master Jay murder '03-'12, 2002-2012 (Box 13, Folder 23)
        - Run-DMC '03, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 24)
        - "Run's Words of Wisdom" '04, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 25)
        - Run-DMC '04, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 26)
        - "Run's House" -- reviews of the television show, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 27)
          Bound press clippings
        - Rev Run "Distortion" press release, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 28)
          2 copies
        - Run-DMC reissues '05, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
        - Run's "Words of Wisdom" book, '05-'06, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 30)
        - Run-DMC '05, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 31)
        - Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '05, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 32)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '06, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 33)
        - Run-DMC '06, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 34)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '07, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - Run-DMC '07, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '08, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - Run-DMC '08, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 4)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '09, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - Run-DMC '09, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '10, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '11, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - Run-DMC '11, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - "Rev Run's Words of Wisdom" '12, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - Run-DMC '12, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 11)
        - Run-DMC '13, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 12)
        - DMC's "Checks, Thugs, and Rock and Roll", 2005 (Box 14, Folder 13)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" book business, c. 1987-1988, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 14)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" book press, etc, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" cover mock-up, No Date (Box 14, Folder 16)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" (book), 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 17)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" agreement w/Russell Simmons and Run, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 18)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" photos, 1987, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 19)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" book rights reversion, 1987, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" book, reissued '02, 2002-2003, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 21)
        - "Run-DMC" liner notes, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
        - "Tougher Than Leather" movie, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Eric Sadler, No Date (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Salt-N-Pepa, 1986-2008 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Sampling, 1988-2012 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Sampling CTI Records, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Schoolly D, 1986-1995, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Scorpio, 1986-1992, 2004-2007 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Select Records, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Sequence, c. 2007 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Serious Lee Fine, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Sam Sever, 1991, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Julian Shabazz, c. 1993 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Shabba Ranks, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - MC Shan, 1987-2009 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Al Sharpton, 1989, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Shinehead, No Date (Box 14, Folder 38)
        Single photograph
      - Hank Shocklee/S.O.U.L. Records, 1988-2006, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Danny Simmons
        - Danny Simmons, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 40)
        - Danny Simmons novel, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - John Singleton, 1992, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 42)